JONGSUN PARK

• DETAILS •

1 Saint Alphonsus Rd
Dundalk, Louth. A91 V1K7
(+353) 87 388 3948
jongsun250@gmail.com
linkedin/in/jongsun-park

• SKILLS •

Client Side Programming

(HTML, CSS, JavaScript)

JavaScript Library

(jQuery, Reactjs, Redux, Nextjs, Gatsby)

Server Side Programming

(PHP, Nodejs, Express)

Design Tools

(Photoshop, Illustrator, AdobeXD, figma)

Design Process

(Prototyping, Persona, Branding)

Repository Management

(github)

Hosting Management

(GoDaddy, Netlify, 1&1, heroku)

CMS

(Wordpress, Shopify, webflow)

PROFILE

I'm a highly self-motivated and self-taught developer and designer.

My first experience in the digital industry is building websites by CMS(WordPress). I used my spare time to learn new skills and trends. It boosts my working speed and results.

I'd like to learn the core of programming and design to achieve efficiency for both client and user. And to keep an eye on trends with new tech to not become outdated.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Developer

JUNE 2021 - NOW

- Built 3 shopify websites and 5 wordpress websites and manage theme.
- Create custom template and features and publishing posts and updates.

Junior Web Developer at Fat Fish Marketing, IRE

DEC 2018 - APR 2020

- Creating WordPress, Shopify website for small client.
- Using AdobeXD and React to create dashboard for analytics dashboard.
- Built SPA for distributing a presentation for shareholders.

General Manager at HANSSEM, KO

JAN 2015 - SEP 2017

• Sale to retail customers and meeting with HQ coworkers as store manager. also manage private marketing and have responsibility for entire sales in the shop.

EDUCATION

Certificate in User Experience Design (LV 7) at DKIT, IRE

FEB 2021 - CURRENT (Ends 2022)

Certificate in Programming (LV 6) at DKIT, IRE

SEP 2018 - SEP 2019

Business Administration and Chinese Literature at Yeungnam University, KR

(NFQ Level 8 / Honours Bachelor Degree Equivalent) MAR 2008 - MAR 2015

u CERTIFICATES (UDEMY)

Programming

- Become a WordPress Developer: Unlocking Power With Code by Brad Schiff
- Complete WordPress Developer Course Plugins & Themes by Luis Ramirez Jr
- NodeJS The Complete Guide (MVC, REST APIs, GraphQL, Deno) by Maximilian Schwarzmüller
- React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux) by Maximilian Schwarzmüller
- The Advanced Web Developer Bootcamp by Colt Steele
- React and Typescript: Build a Portfolio Project by Stephen Grider

Design

- Graphic Design Masterclass Learn GREAT Design by Lindsay Marsh
- Complete Web Design: from Figma to Webflow to Freelancing by Vako Shvili
- Design Mobile Apps: UI, UX & Prototyping in Adobe XD & PS by Cristian Doru Barin
- Master Web Design in Photoshop by Cristian Doru Barin
- Master Digital Product Design: UX Research & UI Design by Rob Sutcliffe

LANGUAGES

- Korean Native
- English Intermediate
- Chinese Intermediate